Mohamed Ramadan Sharkawey

Front End Developer

Professional summary

A team player with over two years of experience began and continued my journey with continuous learning mindset passionate enough to build cool UX and try to be creative enough to make them outstanding, I feel Comfortable in agile environments and ready to make a positive impact to my team.

Contact

+201018845767

Mohamed.sharkawey.77@gmail.com https://mohamed-sharkawey.vercel.app/

Experience

Front end developer, Montech Software studios

Dec 2021 - July 2023, remotely - USA

Developing and maintaining projects in agile environment using multiple technologies like next.Js && React.js.

Maintaining company website and responsible for the monthly newsletter on mailchimp.

Full stack developer intern, Minority programmers Association July 2021 – oct 2021, remotely – USA

Developing and working with multinational team in company website.

Worked in the front end side building features with react.js.

Worked in the back end side with mongoDB mainly used aggregation.
to build a recommendation system feature in the company web app.

Skills

Html, Css, Tailwind

JavaScript & TypeScript

Next.Js & React.js

MUI, AntD & Sass

Redux.js, Socket.io, React query.

node.js, mongoDb & SQL (basics)

Mailchimp campaigning

Full Stack Developer Intern, Tech For Good

Apr 2021 – Jun 2021, remotely – USA learned how to work in agile environment and how to deal with working remotely with multinational team.

Latest Projects

Montech Studios inc Website. https://www.montech.io/

Block Chess Club.

https://www.blokchessclub.com/

UgoFlip Website.

https://www.ugoflip.com/

Allafia Solutions Website.

http://www.alaafiasolutions.com/

Languages

Arabic, Native English, Fluent

Education

Alexandira University, Alexandria - Egypt Bachelor of Civil Engineering